thelisaann.com 2015-06-07

# Danger Enterprises Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**   
Online privacy is constantly evolving and Danger Enterprises, Inc. plans to take all reasonable efforts to maintain up to date and effective online privacy standards and practices. We have linked every page of our website ("Website") to this page for your convenience and you may also contact us at info@dangerenterprises.com with any questions or concerns that you may have.   
Danger Enterprises, Inc. is committed to respecting your online privacy and recognizes the need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. In order to provide payment processing, billing and fraud detection services, Danger Enterprises, Inc. collects and uses your Personal Information. Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home, payment information, and website usernames/passwords. This policy explains how we intend to treat your Personal Information.  
If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on our Website, we may transfer your Personal Information within Danger Enterprises, Inc. or to Danger Enterprises, Inc.'s Third-Parties, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world.  
Danger Enterprises, Inc. strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Danger Enterprises, Inc. intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an "adequate" level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.  
To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles:  
* Notice  
* Choice  
* Security  
* Access/Accuracy  
**NOTICE** **  
****Information Collection**   
You may access and browse our Website without disclosing any Personal Information. However, if you attempt to use Danger Enterprises, Inc.'s services to purchase a product or service online, Danger Enterprises, Inc. may request that you voluntarily supply it with Personal Information. Danger Enterprises, Inc. uses a secure transmission method for all of its transmissions. Danger Enterprises, Inc. receives and stores all information that you enter in our Website and billing pages. In addition, Danger Enterprises, Inc. collects information about you during your visit, such as your IP Address and Danger Enterprises, Inc. employs its software in order to ascertain your physical location when making a purchase. Except as set forth below, Danger Enterprises, Inc. does not collect information from other sources such as public records, or private organizations. However, Danger Enterprises, Inc. does collect Personal Information you submit to Danger Enterprises, Inc.'s Website and its clients in order to complete processing online transactions. You are required to provide Danger Enterprises, Inc. and its clients with accurate and up to date information, and your failure to accurately provide such information could result in the voiding of your agreement(s) with Danger Enterprises, Inc..  
**Information Use**  
Danger Enterprises, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on its Website. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to Third Parties, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Danger Enterprises, Inc. shall release data when required by law, to enforce its agreement(s) with you, or to enforce the contract rights of its clients.  
**Information Sharing**  
We ensure that your Personal Information will not be disclosed to anyone other than a government institution or authority when required by law or other regulation, Danger Enterprises, Inc.'s affiliated merchant bank and card processors as required to process online transactions, and website owners/operators from which you are purchasing goods and services using Danger Enterprises, Inc. ("Third Parties").  
**CHOICE**  
You may choose whether or not to provide Personal Information to Danger Enterprises, Inc.. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of Danger Enterprises, Inc.'s Website, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you. If you chose to have a relationship with Danger Enterprises, Inc., such as a contractual or other business relationship or partnership, you will be required to provide Personal Information in connection with such relationship.  
**SECURITY**  
We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the Personal Information that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. Danger Enterprises, Inc. utilizes Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software when receiving and transmitting electronic payments. Danger Enterprises, Inc. encrypts the sensitive information that you provide. Danger Enterprises, Inc. reveals your credit card number when communicating on a private dedicated line of communication with our associated financial institution.  
In addition, Danger Enterprises, Inc. protects your Personal Information off-line. Security cards are used to enter our facility. All employees and data processors, who have access to and are associated with the processing of Personal Information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your Personal Information. Danger Enterprises, Inc. conducts background and credit checks on all of its employees prior to employment. Danger Enterprises, Inc. employs a User ID and password scheme in order to limit and achieve access to our computer network by our employees and Third Parties.  
**ACCESS/ACCURACY**  
**Access**  
You may inquire about your Personal Information being held by Danger Enterprises, Inc. by sending an email to support@dhdmedia.com. Upon meeting certain security measures, Danger Enterprises, Inc. shall provide you with a copy of the Personal Information that it keeps about you. Danger Enterprises, Inc. may charge a $25 processing fee for the request. Prior to completing your request, Danger Enterprises, Inc. will require that you provide us with certain items as a proof of your identity. Danger Enterprises, Inc. reserves the right to refuse any request for information, though it will communicate the reason for its decision.  
**Accuracy**  
To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, Danger Enterprises, Inc. wishes to maintain accurate Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on our Website, our goal is to provide a means of contacting us should you need to update or correct that Personal Information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your Personal Information to info@dangerenterprises.com and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.  
**COOKIES**  
Danger Enterprises, Inc. uses "cookie" technologies on some portions of Danger Enterprises, Inc.'s Website for the limited purpose of assisting our clients in identifying affiliates which have generated sales. Cookies used by Danger Enterprises, Inc. will only store data associated with the affiliate code derived from the banner or link used to make a purchase. Danger Enterprises, Inc.'s cookies will store no other information about you.  
You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our Website.  
Please note that the use of cookies is optional and setting your browser to block cookies will not affect your ability to make the purchase on any of the websites for which Danger Enterprises, Inc. processes online transactions.  
**THIRD PARTIES**  
Occasionally, Danger Enterprises, Inc. receives information from Third Parties to compare it to information that you had provided to Danger Enterprises, Inc. for fraud prevention purposes.  
Any websites displayed to you by our Website as Internet search results or linked to Internet search results pages provided to you by our Website, including websites owned or operated by our clients, have been developed by Third Parties over which Danger Enterprises, Inc. exercises no control. Such websites may send their own cookies to end users, collect data, or solicit Personal Information from you. Danger Enterprises, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, including such websites' use of any information collected when you are directed to or click through to such websites. Even though such information might not identify you personally, we strongly encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of those websites.  
**DATA PROTECTION SAFE HARBOR POLICY**  
Danger Enterprises, Inc. is a participant in the Safe Harbor program for Data Protection developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union, and is listed by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Danger Enterprises, Inc. has certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles. Danger Enterprises, Inc. uses the self assessment method of verification of compliance. Individuals who believe their privacy may have been violated based on the Safe Harbor privacy principles should contact us at support@dhdmedia.com. For more information about the Safe Harbor program and to view our certification, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor website.  
**MINORS PROTECTION**  
Danger Enterprises, Inc. does not request, or knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 18. Danger Enterprises, Inc. does not give anyone under the age of 18 the ability to post messages or otherwise distribute information about themselves on our Website or allow anyone under the age of 18 to access our Websites.  
**POLICY CHANGES**  
We will make reasonable efforts to maintain an up to date and effective online privacy policy. As such we reserve the right, at any time, to add, change, update, or modify this privacy policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on our Website and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on our Website.  
**COMMITMENT**  
We are committed to privacy and are actively involved in and support current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Danger Enterprises, Inc.'s Website is constantly evolving to meet these demands.  
If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@dhdmedia.com. While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities and as soon as possible.
